I want to be an actor.
P'Sun, do you want to try this?
You don't have to call me P'. Just call me Sun.
The only way you'll pass the audition is by sucking up to the higher-ups.
But as for that Khajohn...
If he doesn't have anyone’s  good in his hands,
then he probably won't last any longe herer in this company.
Oh my god!
If you're not ready to be an actor,
I think it's better if you leave now.
It's a waste of everyone’s time.
I’m asking, who is it?
Hey, do you think you're such a big shot around here?
Bumping into me and not even apologizing?
And still not apologizing? Dumbass!
Do you want to get beaten up?
Are you going to apologize to my bro?
Fine. If you’re not doing anything,
just consider this is your karma then.
Just consider this is your karma then.
Hello?
I have something I want to ask.
Who the hell is he?
If you don't know, then go find out.
Find a way to get rid of him.
How you do it is your business.
Just make sure he can't survive here.
I’m hanging up now.
Who's there?
I’m asking, who is it?
It's me.
I thought that up here was supposed to be a quiet and peaceful place.
Why do I have to come across such a loud racket like this?
I'm sorry.
I happened to hear a strange noise,
So I thought someone was eavesdropping on my phone call.
I didn't expect it to be...
Is what you were talking about that important?
To the point that you have to care for someone to eavesdrop?
Or is it because it's about you wanting to get rid of the new kid?
It's just a misunderstanding.
I just want to do a little prank. That’s all.
And I want to smoke a cigarette up here all alone.
If I knew I'd run into you, I would have brought more cigarettes.
Next time, may I join you up here for a smoke?
Do you not understand the word "alone"?
Are you going to leave anytime soon?
Alright.
You can come out now, Two-Baht Guy.
It’s him right? The one that you're planning to take revenge on?
I’m asking you now if that ass kisser actor
is the one you're planning to take revenge on.
I’m not obligated to tell you.
People are gossiping all over the building you know?
About you bringing a knife to the audition.
Seriously, what were you thinking?
That acting like that would make the judges like you?
Passing the audition in one shot
doesn't mean you're skilled.
Or that you have any talent.
If someone like you really wants to get revenge,
you need to rise to a much higher spot than he is.
These days if you don’t have any backers you’re hopeless.
You’ll never get there on your own.
Mind your own business.
The reason you don't want me meddling in this
is because you probably already have a backer in mind, right?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Is it Director Arthur?
Director Arthur has people to track someone down?
Who is that person?
I don't know either, bro.
But I heard that the Director met this person like five years ago.
Come to think of it, it's quite interesting.
Becoming an actor just to get revenge.
Anyway if you want me to help with anything
whenever it is
what are you going to pay me back with?
Think about that too just in case.
Oh.
And don't forget to pay for my cigarette.
Anyways if you want me to help with anything
whenever it is,
what are you going to pay me back with?
Think about that too just in case.
Damn it.
Dummy.
Angie, eat carefully sweetie. It's hot.
Now that you've passed the audition
the next step is to take profile pictures
to send to the artist management department so they can pitch you to clients.
We need to make them look as good as possible.
You'll shoot with our photographer here at Dream.
And Sun, you also need to update your resume and send it to HR.
You don't happen to have a criminal record, right?
I've been arrested and taken to the police station about 4 or 5 times.
You two haven’t been arrested before?
Have you?
Sky, can I have that notebook?
Here you go.
Please watch Angie for a moment.
Sure.
1. Dropped out of school.
2. No acting experience.
3. Doesn't use social media.
4. Cannot speak English.
5. Has been arrested by the police.
Angie have you ever played Rock-Paper-Scissors?
Yes, I have.
Wanna play with me?
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
See? Love conquers all.
What are you guys playing?
Rock-Paper-Scissors. Look!
That's so cheesy right? Sweetie.
It's not cheesy at all.
Really?
Move now.
Do you know what the advantage of being an ordinary, unknown person is?
It allows us to do whatever we want. Eat whatever we want, go wherever we want.
Although you have to enjoy this feeling while it lasts.
Because once you guys become famous
you won't be able to just sit around here anymore.
A toast to both of P'Khajohn's superstars.
Cheers!
Bottoms up.
Hey, it's alright.
I always knew someone like you would make it big one day.
It's really totally fine.
Because there's another path waiting for you, you little shit.
Go on.
Although there's a lot of stuff left
Can you help me deliver these first?
Okay?
From this day forward,
I will devote all the physical and mental strength I have
solely to revenge.
Hello.
Hey, did you get a new haircut?
Oh, no, no, no. Not weird at all.
I think it looks way better than your old, messy style.
You really are
a charming yet pitiful young man.
Come on.
Ready?
The photographers should be waiting at the studio.
Let's go.
Whoa, bro, I thought I wouldn't make it in time.
Didn't you have classes at the university this morning, Sky?
Yes, but the professor cancelled the morning class.
I knew Sun was having his profile photoshoot,
so I came to keep him company.
Oh, please. Do you want to keep him company or just skip class?
Whatever. You have to go back to your faculty for the afternoon class anyway.
Got it?
I know.
But for now, let me tag along with Sun first, okay?
Please? Let me go too.
Fine, fine, fine. Let's go.
Oh, Sun, did you get a new haircut?
That looks so sharp, man. Extremely sharp.
Let's go.
What's so sharp?
Hello.
Hi, I'm Khajohn. I brought my actor for the profile shoot.
Oh, Mr. Khajohn. Actually, there are no photographers available today.
What? What do you mean?
Didn't I call to confirm the schedule yesterday?
I'm not really sure either.
They came in to work as usual this morning,
but then suddenly packed up all their gear and left.
I'll call them myself.
Okay.
Hello, I'm Khajohn.
The one who mentioned yesterday that I'd bring an actor for a profile shoot.
What? All photographers were called to an outside event?
Usually, events provide their own photographers, don't they?
Okay, I get it.
That's all.
*Sigh*
Can't we just go shoot somewhere else?
Well, if we want to shoot elsewhere,
we have to submit paperwork for approval from upper management first.
Otherwise,
we'd have to pay out of our own pockets.
And right now, I'm kind of broke.
Come on, it's fine.
It's okay if we don't shoot today. We still have plenty of time.
Let's go to acting class with Teacher Phueng instead.
Right?
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Sun.
Teacher Phueng.
I can't let him join the class regardless.
I didn't receive any assignment for this.
But the contract clearly states
that Sun can attend classes with you.
It's not that I don't want to teach him.
But this extra...
Extra?
I mean the actor himself
hasn't even signed a contract with the company yet.
He's still just a trainee, isn't he?
I really want to help but I also have to follow company policy.
Please try to understand me too.
Please check this evening's schedule to see if there are other classes.
And update everyone via email, please.
Look, I don't know why you suddenly won't accept any new kid,
even though it was perfectly fine before.
Sky even used to study with you.
Excuse me, teacher.
You aren't intentionally neglecting your duties, are you?
Are you accusing me of being too lazy to teach?
That is now crossing the line, Manager.
These days if you don’t have any backers you’re hopeless.
You’ll never get there on your own.
I have nothing left to say.
I'll take my leave.
Go ahead.
Damn it!
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry about that.
Everything seems so difficult because of me.
It's because of P'Sunny, actually.
It's very obvious that he’s targeting you.
Let me think about what we should do next.
I need to use the toilet.
Hello?
What's up?
Ready to have a backer now?
You said you could help me.
That's why you told me to go think about it.
And have you made up your mind?
Too bad I have nothing to offer you.
So I didn't know what to give you.
I will give you myself.
Therefore, you must pay a deposit first.
The question is, if I have you,
how do I benefit?
I can probably surprise you from time to time.
So, what is it that you want?
P'Khajohn.
Who is the best photographer in this industry?
Well if we're talking about the number one, it would probably be Phakin.
Why do you ask?
I want him to take my pictures.
Are you out of your mind?
Like he'd ever do that for a nobody like you.
His work is top-tier, he's incredibly famous.
And besides, he's the type who won't just shoot anyone unless they really catch his eye.
Anyways he's that good, but...
Forget about him. He's incredibly hard as hell to work with.
We are going to see him now.
How? Who contacted him? Who's paying?
Someone has already arranged it.
Don't tell me that
you’re getting yourself involved with some backer or some shady investor.
- He’s no…
- If so then you shouldn’t.
I'm telling you right now that you need to back off.
It's not worth the risk.
He isn't an investor.
And right now, I don't exactly know who he really is either.
Let's hurry up.
Hey, wait!
Sun!
Hey!
Please come this way and wait for a moment.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
This place is insanely gorgeous.
Wow.
Mr. Phakin.
Who are you guys?
Uh, I'm Khajohn. I'm...
And what are you doing in my house?
I brought Sun here for a profile photoshoot with you.
I'm not doing it.
What do you think this place is? Huh?
You think you can just show up whenever you want?
Next time, if you want to come, you must make an appointment first.
With or without appointment. Does it make any difference?
Because you only choose to shoot people you like anyway.
You're starting to interest me.
Why don't you try...
taking off your shirt for me to see?
Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Only take off what Mr. Phakin has asked you to.
Have you ever worked as a laborer before?
Your muscles don't look like they're from working out.
Oh, Sun has worked many different jobs.
I do any job that pays.
Sounds unusual.
But with a face like this,
you look pretty ordinary.
Seriously, let me ask you.
How can you be so confident you'll survive in this industry?
So, are you going to take my pictures or not?
If not,
I can go find a better photographer.
I'll do it.
But you have to be my nude model in return.
Can you do that?
Deal.
Are you really sure about shooting nude for Mr. Phakin?
Do you even know what that means?
I know.
Then you must know how it'll affect your future.
Can't you call that person to
help you with just the profile, so you don't have to do the nude photoshoot?
I didn't ask him to help with that.
What do you mean?
Then how did you manage to persuade me to bring you here?
I just believed in your words.
My words?
You said I have what it takes to go far.
So I thought that
Mr. Phakin would definitely want to take my pictures.
Thank you, Manager.
But if you didn't ask him to help with this,
then what did you ask him to help with?
P'Na, how is it? Is everything ready?
Got it. Okay.
Lighting is okay.
I think I remember you.
Your name is Sawai?
Sa...
Sabai?
Smile?
My name is Sky.
Sky. Sky, it is.
Come pose for me for a bit.
I need to test the lighting.
Why? Or do you not want me to take photos with the people your manager brought along that badly?
Try turning to look at the camera.
No, it's not that.
Don't forget to take off your shoes.
Okay, let me check the light exposure first.
Move the key light to the left and lower it by one-third.
And move the negative fill slightly closer to the model.
Got it.
Turn sideways a bit.
Either side is fine.
Try turning to look at the camera.
That's enough.
Excuse me, I need to go to the restroom.
What is wrong with you?
Where are you going?
To the restroom.
Sun, hurry up.
Ready?
Wait.
Don't forget to wipe your feet before going in.
Look at the camera.
Ready?
Tilt your head down a bit.
Your eyes are too stiff.
That's not it.
Ugh, seriously?
You really have never modeled before, have you?
Your posture looks unnatural.
And your gaze looks emotionless.
How can someone like this be an actor?
But you do have one advantageous quality.
You aren't camera-shy.
Usually, you aren't really afraid of anything, right?
I've been afraid long enough.
Have you ever had a lover then?
Parents, siblings, or anyone?
No one
No one?
You must have experienced losses before.
Then try to think of what you've lost.
Think of what you want to go back and fix,
but you no longer have the chance to do so.
Exactly like this.
Look into the camera.
Your losses…
You can’t turn back time.
Thank you for your help, Mr. Phakin.
Don't forget what you said either.
Whenever I'm free,
I'll let you know.
I can't believe we got this lucky.
You're amazing, Sun!
Mr. Phakin actually agreed to shoot for you.
You really are something else.
Even before getting famous,
you got a top photographer like Mr. Phakin to do your profile.
Incredible!
Hello, Boss. Guess where I am right now.
Oh, I don't care where you are.
I only care about what you've done.
Teacher Phueng came to complain to me
that you went on a ranting spree at her
about her not letting your trainee join the acting class.
Uh, wait a minute.
Teacher Phueng accused me of going on a ranting spree at her like that?
Exactly.
Do you know that doing this could get your salary docked?
Salary docked?
Wait a minute, Boss.
As an artist manager,
don't I have the right to protect what we are entitled to from the company?
Boss, don't just listen to one side. Please listen to my side too.
I don't care about your reasons. Because right now, the complaint has already reached upper management.
Anyway, when you're free,
come over to receive the complaint notice at the office.
Boss, don't leave just yet. I'm heading back to the office now.
What did Teacher Phueng do?
Filed a complaint with upper management.
Regarding me bringing Sun to the acting class.
Suddenly she accused me of shouting non-stop at her.
We can't just stay on the defensive about this.
Go back to class first, we'll split up here.
As for you, come back to the office with me.
Please look after P'Khajohn.
Khajohn won't tolerate this anymore.
Boss, listen to what happened from my side first.
Today I booked the office photographer for a profile shoot,
but they were suddenly called to Sunny's event out of nowhere.
And when I tried to take Sun to acting class,
Teacher Phueng out of nowhere refused, even though the contract clearly states he can attend.
Boss, do you understand what's really going on now?
It's not that I don't understand.
But right now, the complaint has already reached upper management.
And if you want to find an excuse or defense for yourself, then go find clear evidence.
If you’re just throwing words out there, nobody will believe you.
Just a moment, please.
Hello? How does it feel? I heard your new kid didn't get to shoot his profile.
Plus you got a complaint from Teacher Phueng as well.
This is why you shouldn’t be doing something pointlessly stupid.
Oh, it's good that you called. I actually have something to thank you for.
Thank me? Thank me for what?
Well, if you hadn't called away all the photographers,
my kid wouldn't have gotten a top photographer like Mr. Phakin to do his profile.
Mr. Phakin?
Listen up, Khajohn.
If you're going to brag, keep it within reality.
You? As if you could really work with him.
Are you insane?
Just wait and see his Instagram in the next two or three days.
Mr. Phakin will probably post the photos he took today.
Oh,
as for the matter with Teacher Phueng, I must thank you too.
Since Kru Phueng said she won't accept any more trainees,
the Boss has already approved the order
to arrange a special private acting coach for us.
It won't be hard for me to find out
which coach you ended up getting.
Let me tell, you that whoever has you as a manager won’t survive in this industry.
What are you talking about? What kind of nonsense is this?
I haven't approved anything yet,
about letting you find a private acting coach for your kid.
Come on, Boss. Just wait and see.
Soon enough, someone will file a complaint to cancel your order anyway.
Boss.
It couldn't be any clearer that my kid is being bullied.
I understand.
But still, the lie about getting a photographer like Mr. Phakin to take his pictures is still outrageous.
If you're going to brag, can you keep it reasonable?
I'm not bragging, I'm speaking the truth.
I just got back from Mr. Phakin's studio.
Do you know that the moment Mr. Phakin saw my kid,
he liked him instantly and promised to take his pictures.
I took some behind-the-scenes footage for you to see
as proof too.
Whoa.
Did Mr. Phakin really take his pictures?
Anyway, if someone calls regarding Sun's acting class.
Could you please approve for Sun to study along with the other kids in class.
Oh. Before coming in earlier, you had something to ask him, right?
What do you want to know?
So, what is it that you want?
How big are you in here?
Bigger than you think, perhaps.
Then could you have an employee called in to be scolded?
Who?
My own manager.
I want to know who ordered P'Khajohn to be called in and scolded.
Can't you tell me?
No, I just didn't expect anyone to actually ask this question.
Actually, I received the order from someone else too.
That person only said
if anyone asks, tell them, "Am I big enough, Mr. Two-Baht?"
Something along those lines.
Come to this location now.
Wait a moment, sir.
This club is for members only.
Non-members are not allowed to enter.
Or you can provide the name of the person you came with.
We will check today's guest list for you.
Uh...
Who did you come with, sir?
Hello.
You are Two-Baht, right?
Two-Baht?
It's an alias used by the client.
I'll take over from here.
Okay, sir.
Please go ahead.
Please come this way, Mr. Two-Baht.
Please, this way.
Follow me, please.
He is waiting for you in there.
Please.
Have a seat.
Who are you really?
A partner.
To be exact, one of the partners.
Meaning a partner of this place?
And what is your name?
What about yours?
Before asking for someone else's name,
why don’t you tell me your own first?
Or do you prefer the name "Mr. Two-Baht"?
Sun.
Jay.
Remember what I once told you?
Nothing in this world comes for free.
Now, the fee for having me scold your manager has increased by another fifty thousand.
The cigarette fee is two hundred thousand.
The question is, are you ready to pay me back?
I only have myself.
You've come all the way here,
what are you expecting?
Have you ever imagined
that I would suddenly make a move on you?
Putting what is mine inside of you?
You've come all the way here, what are you expecting?
What do I need to do to get a chance to get to Director Arthur?
I must find out who you really are.
Focus well on your studies.
Don't screw it up.
I'm Tuo.
I'm Wave.
You probably won't even last a month.
Get the hell out, you worthless piece of shit.
If you want to have a future in this industry,
you have to make good use of your mouth.